Front End Developer SARA MUNIR

+4379846134 📞 🔲 https://github.com/SaraMunir

saramunir011@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/sara-munir

Toronto, Canda (9)

www.saramunir.com

SKILLS

Languages & Databases:

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SCSS, MySQL, NoSQL (MongoDB), FireBase Frameworks & Libraries:

Node(Express), React, Mongoose, Bootstrap, ¡Query, Bootstrap

Git, RESTful APIs, Heroku, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe illustrator, Autocad, 3dMax, Photo

ABOUT ME

I am a web developer with experience in building applications with REACT, javascript(vanilla & ES6+), HTML5, CSS3, Nodejs, MySql, MongoDb and API integration.

With a background in architecture I have developed complex problem solving and design skills which helped me create aesthetically pleasing and yet functional solutions to meet the clients' needs. I left that role with a strong sense of visual design elements like color, typography, and layout with years of training as well as a strong systematic thinking ability, which allows me to focus on figuring out the big pictures before jumping into the details.

EXPERIENCE

Abon Pharmaceuticals

Toronto, Ontario, 2020

Freelance Web developer

Redesigning and rebuilding companies' outdated website from scratch.

Teleperformance

Toronto, Ontario, 2018 - 2019

Customer Service Associate

- Successfully organized and reviewed warranty claims by the customers.
 - Elaborately explained to customers different policies on warranties.

REE ARCHITECTS

Dhaka, Bangladesh, 2015-2017

Associate Architect

• Prepared scale drawings and architectural designs, using computer-aided design or other tools. • Created complex graphics and 3d modeling renderings, using independent judgment, creativity, and computer equipment.

VISTAARA ARCHITECTS

Dhaka, Bangladesh, 2013-2015

Junior Architect

- successfully Illustrated architectural plans and designs as per the senior architects vision, using up to date architectural technology.
- communicated successfully with other department for smooth operation of construction
- Incorporated industry standards for developing and finalizing building plans for construction

PROJECTS

Ecommerce Website:

REACT | CSS | NODE JS | MONGO DB | BOOTSTRAP A full stack MERN application with CRUD operation. It is a basic ecommerce website that allows users to shop for clothing of their choice.

Live: https://github.com/SaraMunir/myEcommerce **GitHub:** https://my-ecommerce-web.herokuapp.com/

Movie Maniax:

REACT | CSS | NODE JS | MONGO DB | BOOTSTRAP | API Movie Maniax is a user-friendly movie search application built on MERN stack that allows users to search for movies, add movies to watchlist as well as to favorites list. Users can also add other users as their friend and view their favourite list, watchlist and reviews.

Live: https://github.com/jsanthos01/MovieManiax GitHub: https://movie-maniax.herokuapp.com/

A Game Of Thrones Trivia:

HTML5 | CSS | SCSS | JAVASCRIPT | API

Movie Maniax is a user-friendly movie search application built on MERN stack that allows users to search for movies, add movies to watchlist as well as to favorites list. Users can also add other users as their friend and view their favourite list, watchlist and reviews.

Live: https://house-juno.github.io/SaraSeanProject2/ GitHub: https://github.com/House-Juno/SaraSeanProject2

EDUCATION

Juno College of Technology | Wev development Immersive | 2021, Toronto, Canada

School of Continuing Studies, University of Torontoy | Full Stack Web Flex course | 2020, Toronto, Canada

Ahsanullah University of Science and Technology | Bachelor of Architecture | 2013, Dhaka, Bangladesh